Hello, welcome to this educational video
about artificial intelligence and machine learning.
Today we will explore the fascinating world of neural networks
and deep learning algorithms.
Machine learning is transforming many industries
including healthcare, finance, and transportation.
Neural networks mimic the way human brains process information
through interconnected nodes called neurons.
Deep learning uses multiple layers of these networks
to recognize complex patterns in data.
This technology enables computers to understand images,
recognize speech, and translate languages.
The applications are virtually limitless
and continue to grow every day.
Thank you for watching this introduction to AI and ML.
EOF < /dev/null